hoolapp.com 2013-05-08

# Privacy Policy | Hoolapp – Desktop to Android

**Privacy Policy**

 **Privacy Policy -  Hoolapp**

[Last Updated May 8, 2013]

IronSource Ltd. and its affiliates (“IronSource” or “we“) respect the privacy of HoolApp’s users (“User” or “you“) and are committed to protect the User’s information. We believe that you have a right to know our practices regarding the information we may or may not collect and use when you use the HoolApp’s website available at: www.hoolapp.com, HoolApp software (“HoolApp Platform”) and related services via your computer and/or mobile device (“Device”) (collectively the “Service“).

* * *

****BY ACCESSING AND/OR USING THE SERVICE, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DISAGREE TO ANY TERM PROVIDED HEREIN, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE SERVICES.****

* * *

  * We do not collect, use or share any of your information except for the purpose of identify your Device when you log-in to the Service and to assure successful installation of mobile application on your Device.

  * This Privacy Policy does not apply any third party mobile applications promoted via the Hoolapp Platform nor their practices, therefore we recommend that you read carefully all relevant privacy policies of such third parties’ before using their mobile applications, websites and/or services .

  * IronSource reserves the right to amend, change and/or update this Privacy Policy from time to time. In case of any material change, we will make reasonable efforts to post a clear notice or announcement on the on the Hoolapp website. Any modifications to this Privacy Policy are effective as of the stated “Last Updated” date herein above. Please note that your continued use of the Service after our “Last Updated” date shall constitute an acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by those revisions. We advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any revisions.

  * The definitions in the Terms of Use apply to this Privacy Policy unless stated otherwise.

What Information do We Collect?

  1. Personal Identifiable Information

In order to use the Service and to download mobile application from Google Play, you would have to be logged-in to your Google account or to conduct a log-in to your Google account via Google's regular log-in procedure or via the Service interface. When you log-in to your Google account you may be asked to provide your email address. This information is managed directly by Google servers and is not collected nor stored by us. Please note that your log-in to your Google account is not part of our registration process, however we may use this information for the purpose of identifying your Device and assuring a successful installation of mobile applications. Note that this information provided by you is subject to Google's privacy policies.

During your first engagement with the Service, and in case you are already logged in ot your Google account, you won’t need to provide us with any Personal Identifying Information, all you need approve to provide us will be your consent that we will access the Google Play Store on your behalf by using your Google Play account. This is required in order to manage the installation and/or uninstallation of your Device’s mobile application and to assure we provide you with the best possible Service.

If you log in to your Google account via the Service interface, We may get access to information that was collected by Google including your e-mail address, your list of Devices and information that identifies your mobile device, such as the International Mobile Equipment Identity, IP address and Device ID. Such Personal Identifiable Information is not stored by us in a readable or accessible manner and is being processed in its hashed and encrypted form for Device matching and management purposes only.

We may also automatically collect data about mobile applications you have installed on your Device and the frequency of their use in order to assist you with your Device management. We may collect details on how you used the Service, such as your browsing behavior and search queries within the Service.

If you voluntarily submit information or contact us (e.g. for technical support), we may keep a record of this communication. We will use this information solely for the purpose of responding to your inquiry. If any Personal Identifiable Information happens to be collected, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the Personal Identifiable Information submitted to us.

During the use of the Service you will be presented with third parties’ mobile application offers. If you decide to download third parties’ mobile application, these third parties may have different privacy policies regarding the information they collect, use or share. We recommend that you read these third parties’ privacy policies for more information about their information collection and privacy practices. We may present you with third parties’ desktop application and therefore we recommend that you read these third parties’ privacy policies as well.

  2. Aggregate Information We Collect

When you use the Service, we may collect anonymous, non-Personal Identifiable Information regarding your Device system, such as your IP address, browser type, the type of operating system you use, details about your Device hardware, the applications you have installed on it, the domain name of your Internet service provider, if Java or .NET was used for the installation and pages you visited on our sites.

This information does not identify you personally; we use this information to help us improve the performance of our Service. All of the above non-Personal Identifiable Information is collected in an aggregate anonymous form.

  3. Cookies

A cookie is a string of data that a website stores on a user's browser while the user is browsing a website, and enables the website to retrieve the data stored on this user when the user browses the same website again.

We do not link the information we store in cookies to any Personal Identifiable Information you submit while you are using our website and/or Services unless you assent to it.

If you wish not to have cookies placed on your browser, you should set your browser to refuse cookies before using the website, with the drawback that certain features of the website may not function properly without the aid of cookies. Furthermore, We may use cookies to correlate between your Device and information stored in our servers. Any information derived from cookie use, will be treated in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

We may also use certain third parties’ cookies, these are a different kind of cookies, stored on your computer by third parties (e.g. Google Play), rather than by us. Such third party cookies usually store only a Non-Personal Identifying Information. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of cookies that may be used by any third party. We also have no control over such cookies and the information they collect and use.

IronSource takes no responsibility for such third party cookies since it has no control over them.

  4. Global Unique Identifiers (GUID)

A GUID is a randomly generated alphanumeric identifier used to indicate a unique installation of our software or Service. We may create a GUID when you use the Service. We use GUID to track installations statistics and to enable features and functionality for our users. We do not associate the information gathered by GUIDs to our users' Personal Identifiable Information.

  5. Log Files

We may gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. Such information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user- base as a whole. We do not associate this automatically collected data with Personally Identifiable Information.

How do We Use Your Information?

We do not collect, share or store any Personal Identifying Information with third parties, we use this information solely for the purpose of providing you with our Service. We might   use your email address, provided by you, in its hashed and encrypted form, to correlate your Google account and your Device in order to install mobile application on your Device. In order to enable the Service, we may further use your Device ID in order to assure successful management (including installation) of mobile application on your Device according to your request.

Do We Share Your Information?

We do not sell or share any of your Personal Identifiable Information to or with third parties. However, we may use your non Personal Identifying Information to Improve the Service and to better customize the features, performance, and support included in the Service;

In addition, we might use your Personal Identifying Information for the following reasons:

  * As required by law and if We will believe that such disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process;

  * If We have a good reason to belief that it is necessary to: (i) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security breach, violation of our policies or to meet critical technical need; (ii) enforce the provisions of this Privacy Policy and/or any other agreements between you and us, including investigation of potential violations thereof; or (iii) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of us, our partners, third parties, visitors, users and/or the public.

  * We may share the unique identifier used by your Device in order to correlate your device ID with your Google Play account and provide you with the Services, and/or to track your installations and assure successful installation of mobile applications.

  * We may transfer or assign all collected information as part of a merger, acquisition, sale or other change of control. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer may continue to use your Personally Identifiable Information and other information as set forth in this policy.

  * We may share your non-private, aggregated, or otherwise non-personal information, such as usage statistics of our Services.

Security

The security of your Personal Identifiable Information is important to us, and we take measures to protect your information. In particular, we store your Personal Identifying Information (e.g. email address) only in its hashed and encrypted form.  However, no method of transmitting or storing electronic data is 100% secure, and therefore we cannot warrant or guarantee that such information will never be accessed, used, or released in a manner that is inconsistent with this policy.

Do We Retain Your Information?

We will not store any Personal Identifying Information; we might store your Personal Identifying Information only in its hashed and encrypted form, in a manner that does not enable to identify you personally.

Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)

In compliance with the COPPA, We will not knowingly collect information about children under the age of 13. We encourage parents and guardians to be familiar with the web sites that their children visit.

Can You Remove or Delete your Information?

You can remove any of your information collected and retains by contacting us at: [privacy@hoolapp.com](mailto:legal@hoolapp.com).
